DANIEL GOZDOLEK

Address: Balbriggan, Co. Dublin Mobile: 087-95-64-503 Email: daniel@webox.ie

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-gozdolek/

Online CV: https://danncti.github.io/cv/

Profile

With a background spanning over 15 years, my journey has revolved around the world of programming and technology. It's been an exploration of software development, including diverse roles and languages like C++, PHP, and Python. My current focus is to work as a Python developer.

A lifelong curiosity for knowledge has led me to dive into the diverse world of Python. As an INTP personality type, complex problems, data analysis, and inventive solutions are my strong suit. Throughout my career, my passion for technology and programming has been a driving force.

Key skills

- Python
 Selenium
 Django
 Git
 Web Scraping
 JavaScript
 Linux
 SQL
 Algorithms
 API
 Automation
 Docker
 Full Stack Developer
 WooCommerce
- Finding solutions to complex issues
 Focussed on achieving goals
 Looking for improvements

Work Experience

Manager - Web Developer

Rangel GDLK Limited, Dublin,

10/2018 - 05/2022

- Responsible for maintaining and updating the websites, security, backups
- Monitoring site traffic and key performance metrics
- Create and update user-friendly, functional and accessible layouts
- Write custom code to update content through WordPress, WooCommerce API, on e-commerce shop

One of the websites was achieved 6.5 millions views in 12 months, and was working fast and stable.

IT Administrator

Eurecca Un Limited, Balbriggan, Co. Dublin

01/2019 - 02/2021

- E-commerce websites development
- IT systems supervision
- PHP and Python e-commerce automation, product updates through API and custom scripts
- Web Scraping using PHP and later Python
- Configuration of Linux server for websites and emails
- Systems configuration, backups, maintenance

Complete design, from idea to working product, of two electronic devices to control photovoltaic trackers, including printed circuit board and sun sensor, and make programs to manage these devices.

IT Administrator,	Happy Paw Training Limited,	01/2017 - 01/2019
Operation supervisor	Balbriggan, Co. Dublin	

- Securing, install and configure users PCs, Laptops, Software etc.
- HubSpot's administration, IT systems supervision
- PHP scripts for e-commerce automatic update (OpenCart, PrestaShop by custom PHP script)
- Backup, security configuration and maintenance of few websites.
- Create professional documents, comply with law regulations to record work processes, and keep all required customers records

Successfully expansion company to new areas. Create all documentation to obtain HACCP Certification.

General Assistant DHL, Swo	rds, Co. Dublin, 07/2006 - 01/2019
----------------------------	------------------------------------

- Making changes and adjustments on delivery schedule on a regular basis
- Tracking reporting and analysing operations performance
- Monitoring and preparation of deliveries

Create and maintaining automatic system to prepare barcode labels for shipment control - Excel VBA

Education and Training

11/2022 - 05/2023	Certiport - A Pearson VUE Business	Information Technology Specialist in Python
02/2022 - 06/2022	Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) (Exam: 98-381)	Introduction to Programming using Python
07/2021 - 09/2021	Google - Professional Certificate	Google IT Automation with Python
11/2021 - 12/2021	University of Michigan - Specialization Certificate - Coursera.org	Python for Everybody
10/2021 - 12/2021	University of California, San Diego Course - Coursera.org	Algorithmic Toolbox & Algorithms on Graphs
09/1999 - 06/2004	Master Degree (NFQ 9)	Pedagogy in Management

Interests

My passion for computer programming dates back to my primary school days, starting with the Commodore 64 manual and periodic newspapers in the late 1980s.

I have continuously engaged in programming throughout various stages of my life, working with languages like C++, PHP, and Python. I also developed a mobile app that was available on the Apple Store for several years.

Additionally, I have a keen interest in human behaviour, psychology, and audiobooks.

References available on request